smcindiaonline.com 2009-06-22

# India Dalal Street, Indian Share Business

| 

**Respecting your privacy and the law**

The privacy of your personal information has always been important to us at the SMC Group (“Group”). We are committed to respecting your right to privacy and protecting your personal information. Our staff are trained to respect your privacy in accordance with our standards, policies and procedures.

**About this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy outlines how we manage your personal information. It also describes generally the sorts of personal information held and for what purposes, and how that information is collected, held, used and disclosed.

Our Privacy Policy applies to all your dealings with us whether at one of our branches, via our websites or an advisor. We encourage you to check our websites regularly for any updates to our Privacy Policy.

**Collecting your personal information**

If you are acquiring or have acquired a product or service from our Group, it will collect and hold your personal information for the purposes of: 

  * providing you with the relevant product or service (including assessing your application and identifying you) 
  * managing and administering the product or service 
  * protecting against fraud where it is a product or service. 

Group may also collect your personal information for the purpose of letting you know about products or services from across the Group that might better serve your needs or promotions or other opportunities in which you may be interested.

The information collected may include your name, postal or email address, date of birth, financial details, PAN number or other information the Group considers necessary.

We will, if it is reasonable or practicable to do so, collect your personal information from you. This may happen when you fill out a product or service application or an administrative form (eg a change of address form) or when you give us personal information over the telephone or counter, or through our website.

**Using and disclosing your personal information**

In line with modern business practices common to many financial institutions and to meet your specific needs (such as where you have a financial adviser) we may disclose your personal information to the organisations described below.

  * involved in providing, managing or administering your product or service such as third party suppliers, other Group organisations, loyalty and affinity program partners, printers, posting services, call centres and our advisers 
  * which are Group organisations who wish to tell you about their products or services that might better serve your needs or promotions or other opportunities, and their related service providers. 
  * involved in maintaining, reviewing and developing our business systems, procedures and infrastructure including testing or upgrading our computer systems 
  * involved in a corporate re-organisation 
  * involved in a transfer of all or part of the assets or business of a Group organisation 
  * involved in product planning and development 
  * which are your representatives including your legal advisers 
  * as required or authorised by law, for example, to government or regulatory bodies for purposes related to public health or safety, the prevention or detection of unlawful activities or to protect public revenue 

**Keeping your personal information accurate and up-to-date**

We aim to make sure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. We will take reasonable steps to make sure this is the case. This way we can provide you with better service.

If you believe your personal information is not accurate, complete or up to date, please contact us. 

**Protecting your personal information**

We store information in different ways, including in paper and electronic form. The security of your personal information is important to us and we take reasonable steps to protect it from misuse and loss and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. Some of the ways we do this are: 

  * document storage security policies 
  * security measures for systems access 
  * only allowing access to personal information where the individual seeking access has satisfied our identification requirements 
  * access control for our buildings 

**Your privacy on the Internet**

We take care to ensure that the personal information you give us on our websites is protected. For example, our websites have electronic security systems in place, including the use of firewalls and data encryption. Depending on the Group organisation with which you deal, user identifiers, passwords or other access codes may also be used to control access to your personal information. 

**Links to Other Sites**

You may be able to access external websites by clicking on links we have provided. Those other websites are not subject to our privacy standards, policies and procedures. You will need to contact or review those websites directly to ascertain their privacy standards, policies and procedures.

**Third-Party Advertisement Servers**

SMC Group engages the services of an outside advertisement company to display advertisement on the Web Site. These advertisements may contain cookies. While SMC Group uses cookies in other parts of the Web Site, cookies received with banner advertisements are collected by the Advertisement company, and SMC Group does not have access to this information.

**Resolving your privacy issues**

If you have any issues you wish to raise with the Group, or would like to discuss any issues about our Privacy Policy, then you are able to do so a number of ways: 

  * You are always welcome to speak directly to our staff at Customer care numbers. 
  * You can email your issue on [info@smcindiaonline.com.](mailto:info@smcindiaonline.com)

|
